# RambodRahmani

Artificial Intelligence Engineer

#### **Contact**

Via Pietro Casu, 16 Sassari, (SS) 07100 Italy

(+39) 333 3840979 (+39) 079 2859049

### Languages

Persian (Mother tongue) Italian (Mother tongue) English (C1) French (A2)



Iran, Italy, Germany, Spain, France, Belgium, Holland, Russia, Hungary.

### Programming •

C, C++, Java, Python, R, OpenCV, OpenCL, OpenGL, Nvidia CUDA, Julia, ROS, Shell Script.

### **Software**

Vim, CLion, Matlab, Visual Studio, Eclipse, OMNeT++, VirtualBox, MongoDB, CassandraDB, Git, R Studio, Jupyter Notebook.

#### **Hardware**

Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Embedded Pi, Cubieboard, NVIDIA Jetson.

# Operating Systems A

Windows 10, Mac OS X, iOS, Android, Linux Debian, Arch Linux, Raspbian, OpenWRT.

# **Summary**

I was born in Iran in 1993 and moved to Italy at the age of 7. I started studying programming languages at the age of 15 and began to work as a freelance programmer a couple of years later. At the age of 19 I was admitted to the University of Pisa as a Computer Engineering student. After finishing my bachelor I enrolled for a Master in Artificial Intelligence and Data Engineering. In the past years, beside studying for my examinations, I worked for IT Companies, I took part in group projects and tried to startup my own ideas. During the academic year 2017/2018, my goals have shifted. I have developed a deep interest in Artificial Intelligence.

### **Education**

2020 - 2022 Master of Engineering Studies - Artificial Intelligence University of Pisa, Italy
2013 - 2019 Bachelor of Engineering Studies - Computer Engineering University of Pisa, Italy
2008 - 2013 High School Diploma 100/100 - Scientific Lyceum Scientific Lyceum "G. Spano", Italy

# **University Projects**

2020 **E-Team Squadra Corse** University of Pisa

Autonomous Vehicle Development

My work focused on the development of the driverless autonomous vehicle.

2019 **Roborace** University of Pisa - E. Piaggio Research Center

Autonomous Vehicle Development

My work focused on the driverless electric vehicle DevBot 2.0.

2015 PHOS Project University of Pisa

Software Programmer

Aerospace project at University of Pisa part of the REXUS/BEXUS programme.

# **Papers**

2012 KerubLess - Design of a Driverless Formula SAE Vehicle

2022 IEEE 5th International Conference on Industrial Cyber-Physical Systems

# **Work Experience**

2020 R.H. Impianti di Rahmani Hamidreza Consorzio di Bonifica della Nurra

Siemens TIA Portal V16 Developer

Design, development and deployment of a remote monitoring infastructure based on Siemens PLC S7-1200, Simatic HMI TP1200, SINAMICS G120X.

2018 ClassX S.r.I. Pontedera

Java Developer

I worked as Java developer for the ClassX S.r.I focusing to develop broadcasting  $\,$ 

software and hardware.

2018 ClassX S.r.l. Pontedera

Intership

Curricular internship Computer Engineering student at University of Pisa.

2013 Ambulatory Proctology Office Sardinia, Italy

Objective-C Software Programmer

I developed the software used to manage patients medical history.

# 3D Printing 🔕

• Geeetech Prusa i3

Anycubic I3 Mega

• Creality Ender 3 Pro

Anycubic Photon

### 11,700,010 1 1101011

### OpenWRT 🤝

As a member of a local hacklab in Pisa, I was involved in installing and configuring the OpenWRT Distribution on embedded devices that we used to build the local **Wireless Mesh Network** EigenNet.

# Bitcoin ₿

I have been involved in Bitcoins as far as it regards Bitcoin Mining, Mining Pools, Bitcoin Wallet and Full Bitcoin Node Configuration (Bitcoin Core).

### Linkedin in

For full and detailed information regarding my work experience, projects and awards please refer to my **Linkedin Profile**: it.linkedin.com/in/rambodrahmani.

# GitHub 😱

"Sharing isn't immoral it's a moral imperative. Only those blinded by greed would refuse to let a friend make a copy."

GitHub Profile:

github.com/rambodrahmani.

#### 2012 **MALIBU Village**

Internship

I worked as IT Support at MALIBU Village as part of the "Leonardo Project" internship. I had a hands-on experience with Ubiquiti Picostations.

2010 - 2012 Italian Navy

San Giorgio-class amphibious transport dock, Italy

Canet-Plage, Languedoc-Roussillon, France

Software Programmer

I coded a set of three software named A.S.C (Acceptance, Sorting and Control) for

the Italian Navy.

2014 - 2015 **Boccaccio Club** 

Pisa, Italy

Software Programmer

Boccaccio Club iOS and Android App Development.

# **Awards, Scholarships and Certificates**

2013 - 2016 **DSU Scholarship** 

DSU of Tuscany

DSU Scholarship by DSU of Tuscany supporting my Bachelor of Engineering

Studies.

2013 - 2016 Italian Ministry of Education, University and Research Scholarship

MIUR

Excellence Scholarship by MIUR supporting my Bachelor of Engineering

Studies.

2012 Intel Excellence in Computer Science

Intel Corporation

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

2012 National Excellence Registry

Italian Ministry of Education, University and Research

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

2012 **Certificate of Merit** 

Scientific Lyceum "G. Spano", Italy

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

2012 **Europass Mobility Nr. IT/00/2012/859/10** 

Gymnasium Lyceum "D. A. Azuni" and ALFMED (Académie de Langues France

Méditerranée.).

2011 A.S.C. Software Italian Navy - San Giorgio-class Amphibious Transport Dock

Software Development Certificate by the Italian Navy for developing the A.S.C.

Software.

### **Events**

May 2015

May 2015 International World Wide Web Conference 2015

Florence, Italy

Berlin, Germany

Research, development, and applications of the topics related to the Web.

May 2015 **HEUREKA 2015** 

One of the main founders conferences in the German-speaking world.

**Berlin Talent Summit 2015**Europe's leading recruiting conference for high-potentials.

July 2012 9th EXPO-SCIENCES EUROPE 2012 (ESE)

Tula, Russia

Berlin, Germany

9th MILSET Expo-Sciences Europe (ESE 2012) held in Tula, Russia.

April 2012 I Giovani E Le Scienze 2012

Federation of Scientific and Technical Associations

The A.S.C. Software was selected as one of the best 30 in the whole country.

### Interests

**Professional:** Computational Complexity, Artificial Intelligence, Artificial Neural Networks, Deep Learning, Symbolic Computation, Statistics, Hardware Accelerators, Cloud Computing, Software design, Linux. **Personal:** Running, Chess, Cosmology, Astronomical observations, Stock Market, Quantitative trading.

Last updated: October 3,

2022